恩 你已经完成了
Alright, you're done!
我们看一下解决方案
Let's take a look at the solution.
对于天气(content provider)我们仅仅获得一个可读的数据库和
For weather,
we just get a readable database and
传递请求content provider来的所有参数
pass all of these parameters
from the content provider call.
天气和位置的实现方法是相当类似的
The solution for weather and
location is pretty much the same.
对于每一个 我们传递从content provider来的参数
For each one, we're going to pass the
parameters that come through the content
到可读的数据库中的查询方法
provider into the query function
of our readable database.
再次提醒 这些参数是从content provider中来的
Again, these are the parameters that
come through the content provider, and
这些参数的我们要传递给数据库的
these are the parameters that
we pass into the database.
位置(的content provider)看起来是类似的
Location looks approximately the same.